const clues = [
	{
		question:
			"I am the silent partner in your typing dance,Without me, shortcuts wouldn’t stand a chance. One would stand who lies in fourth of the  line in curvy shape. From text to files i lead the way , what combo am I used everyday. HINT: keyboard ",
		answer: "Paris",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I am not a tree, yet I let you rest in the open air , I stand in the middle watching the cricket pitch all day. Let me know how many siblings do I have in your way.",
		answer: "Berlin",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I mold engineers in ways unexpected, even their patience get tested and perfected ,I am a place of spark and flame , I am the other half of my name.",
		answer: "Rome",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I smell of spice, I echo with cheer, at lunch and snacks you will find me near . not a classroom yet a lesson’s learnt , about good food and meals well earned! Where am I?? My one of the table has the key, and it will get you to victory.",
		answer: "Madrid",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I am not a number but I am found in maths, A twist of symbols shows my path In digital chit chat , i quietly appear , A small sign of affection,warm and sincere. HINT: Symbol",
		answer: "Lisbon",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I once held crowds and echoed cheer,But now I’m quiet — no one’s near. My walls are bare, my floor's torn wide, Yet something new is built inside. Step by step, you climb with care, Count me right — I’ll take you there. HINT: A spot in college",
		answer: "Athens",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I’m Apple’s voice, polite and sleek, Ask me anything — I’ll let you speak. I call, I text, I guide your ride, Just say “Hey” — I’m by your side.",
		answer: "Amsterdam",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I’m not a dot, I’m not a comma, I end the line without the drama. In code, I’m king — miss me, you’ll cry, The program breaks, but no goodbye.",
		answer: "Brussels",
	},
	{
		question:
			"I stand in a corner, quiet but bright, When exams are near, I’m bustling with might. Pens, paper, tools—whatever you need, I’m the place where knowledge takes seed. I have a QR other than the PhonePay one, Scan me and get close to number one.",
		answer: "Bern",
	},
	{
		question:
			"In the land of wheels where silence roars, Seek the steed with crimson oars, By the gate or near the tree, Its red mark flutters wild and free. Look not at brands or shiny gloss, But seek the tail of metal horse, Its last two digit bold and bright, will end your quest and feel just right.",
		answer: "Vienna",
	},
];

module.exports = { clues };
